Subindex build by Linnet
http://linnet.126.com  http://blog.csdn.net/redbirdli
火鸟字幕合并器SubindexV0.5
Created time 09.09.07 23:45:54
我是坐到什么东东啊?
What am I sitting on?
世界顶端?河堤码头? (歌词)
Top of the worId?
Dock of the bay?
想不出来了
I'm out.
内裤
Oh, undies!
老实说,谁的?
Whose are they?
谁的?
-Whose are they? -Not mine.
不是我的
Joey's! Got to be Joey's.
是乔伊的,一定是他的
的确是我的
They're mine.
看吧?就是乔伊的,乔…伊的
See, Joey's. They're Joe-Joe-Joey's.
怎么会在这里?
Why are they here?
我不知道…
I don't know.
因为我是乔伊
I'm Joey.
我生性龌龊 随便在别人家脱内裤
I'm disgusting.
I take my underwear off in other peopIe's homes.
快拿走,你哪里有病啊?
Get them out of here. What's wrong with you?
对啊 好恶
拿去啊
-Take them! -I got them.
乔伊,你干嘛不敢碰 这是你的内裤
You can touch them. They're yours.
钱德,借一步说话 好
ChandIer? A word?
我受够了 不想再帮你们说谎了
I'm tired of covering for you two. This has got to stop.
这种鸟事不能再发生了
而且还是白色三角裤?
Tighty-whiteys? What are you, 8?
你8岁吗?
谢谢你,乔伊,感激不尽
Thank you, Joey, so much.
我家不欢迎你
You're not weIcome, okay?
我讨厌这样
Look, I hate this. You guys keep embarrassing me.
你们害我拼命出丑
昨天瑞秋在这里的浴室 看到你的剃刀
Yesterday, RacheI found your razor in our bathroom.
我不知道怎么回答
I said it was mine, and that I was pIaying a woman in a pIay.
只好说是我的
还说我要在话剧里演女人
结果还得一不做二不休
Then one thing Ied to another, and....
连脚踝周围都剃光了 那里很不好刮哩
And around the ankIes, that is a tough spot.
没错,告诉你们,我不能…
It was. AII right, Iisten--
我们要说谎也不好受
AII this Iying has been hard on us too.
是喔,不过至少你们有上床
Yeah, I bet aII the sex makes it easier.
那倒是
Yeah, actuaIIy.
瑞秋不仅把你的内裤 凑到我面前
MeanwhiIe, I get RacheI shoving your underwear in my face...
还问什么时候 可以看我演出丑女人
...and asking when she can come see me star in Ugly Woman.
我们下次一定会更小心
We'II be more carefuI.
因为我们实在太甜蜜了 所以不想告诉别人
We don't want them to know because it's going reaIIy weII.
搞不好就是保密才能这么顺利
And maybe it's going weII because it's a secret.
我知道你觉得很怪 但我们都不太会处理感情问题
It sounds weird, but we're so bad at reIationships.
没错,帮帮忙 拜
-We are. HeIp us! -HeIp!
好吧,不过…
AII right. But you do it with me once.
你要跟我上床一次
乔伊 就知道你不肯
-Joey! -Didn't think so.
本集播出：“真相不白”
The One With Ross' Sandwich
欢迎光临 淘宝店--迷失蔚蓝 lost in blue (PSP影视\游戏) http://shop34826882.taobao.com/
不能换个话题吗?
-Can we pIease just drop this? -But I don't get it.
可是我实在不懂
Does anybody eIse just take off their underwear when they're hot?
别人一热也会随便 在朋友家脱内裤吗?
菲比
菲比 嗨,菲比
What are you reading?
你在看什么?
“咆哮山庄”
Wuthering Heights.
我在纽恩大学上文学课 明天之前必须看完
I have to finish it by tomorrow for my Iiterature cIass.
我不知道你在上课,真酷
You're taking a cIass? That's so cooI.
上次上拉梅兹课很好玩
I reaIIy Iiked that Lamaze cIass I took.
所以我决定换种课来上 换点比较要用脑袋
I thought this time I'd go for something more inteIIectuaI...
期末考又不用那么痛苦的
...with a Iess painfuI finaI exam.
听起来很有意思
That sounds Iike fun.
你也可以一起来
Oh, you shouId come with me!
就有人可以跟我一起坐了
Then I'II have someone to sit with.
好啊
不过你有时间看书吗?
Do you have time to read it?
我高中就过那本了
I read it in schooI.
一定很好玩 制片：珊
This is going to be so much fun! I have to finish.
嘘,先让我看完
制片：史考特席维利
几点要上课?
But what time does the cIass start?
别吵
嗨 编剧：安德鲁瑞屈、泰德柯恩
你怎么啦?
What's wrong, buddy?
有同事偷吃我的三明治
Someone at work ate my sandwich.
条子怎么说? 导演：盖瑞哈瓦森
What did the poIice say?
那是感恩节剩下的三明治 竟然给人偷吃掉
My Thanksgiving Ieftover sandwich.
I can't beIieve someone ate it.
不过是个三明治嘛
It's just a sandwich.
不过是个三明治?
Just a sandwich?
我今年30岁,已经离婚两次 还没地方可住
I am 30 years oId, okay?
I'II be divorced twice and I got evicted.
那个三明治是我人生中 唯一美好的事情
That sandwich was the onIy good thing in my Iife!
结果唯一美好的事情 竟然给人偷吃掉
Someone ate the onIy good thing going on in my Iife!
这件毛背心不错
That's a nice sweater vest.
我还有材料可以再做一个
I have enough for one more sandwich.
我本来自己要吃…
I was going to eat it myseIf, but....
太好了,真是谢谢你
Mon, that wouId be incredibIe. Thank you so much.
我到现在还不相信有人偷吃了
I stiII can't beIieve someone ate it!
我还留了一张纸条在上面
Look, I Ieft a note and everything.
“叩叩叩”,“谁啊?”
''Knock-knock.'' ''Who's there?''
“罗斯盖勒的午餐”
''Ross GeIIer's Iunch.''
“哪个罗斯盖勒的午餐?”
''Ross GeIIer's Iunch, who?''
“这是罗斯盖勒的午餐 请勿偷走我”
''Ross GeIIer's Iunch. PIease don't take me. Okay?''
你没被扁就该偷笑了
I'm surprised you didn't wear it home.
不想让别人偷吃你的东西?
Want to keep your food? Scare peopIe off.
那就得吓跑他们 这是我在街头流浪学到的
I Iearned that on the street.
真的?不然你怎么说,菲比?
ReaIIy?
What wouId you say, Pheebs?
例如“脏手少碰我的馊水”?
Stuff Iike: ''Keep your mitts off my grub.''
罗斯,你以为菲比 当年是在演温苦女流浪记吗?
Do you picture Phoebe on the street with the entire cast of Annie?
贴上这张纸条就没人敢偷吃了
This'II keep them away from your stuff.
哇
菲比,你真狠
Phoebe, you are a badass!
下次再告诉你们 我拿刀捅条子的事
Someday I'II teII you how I stabbed the cop.
菲比
He stabbed me first!
是他先捅我的
布朗蒂姐是当代的杰出女性
The Bront? sisters were remarkabIe women for their time.
当时是父系社会
They Iived in a patriarchaI society.
抱歉迟到,因为我太晚出门
Sorry I'm Iate, but I Ieft Iate.
菲比,这本书在说什么?
So, what is the book about?
你说你高中过
Didn't you read it in high schooI?
对,后来我想起我开始看时 正好碰上要为球队打气
I started it, but then there was this pep raIIy.
我又是啦啦队队长
And I was on top of the pyramid.
就是这样啦…到底在说什么?
But anyway...
...what's the book about?
这是凯西跟希克里夫 的悲惨爱情故事
It's a tragic Iove story between Cathy and HeathcIiff.
故事发生在英国可怕的山庄
It takes pIace on these creepy moors in EngIand.
场景就代表 男主角性格中狂野的一面
Which I think represent the wiIdness of HeathcIiff's character.
我对象征主义很有一套
I totaIIy get symboIism.
这本书的主题是什么?
How wouId you characterize the theme of this book?
看看找谁…瑞秋葛林
Let's see.... RacheI Greene?
这是个…爱情悲剧
I wouId have to say that it's a tragic Iove story.
非常明显,不过你说得也没错
That's sort of a given...
还有谁有意见?
...but, yes. Anyone eIse?
还有象征性的意义
SymboIism!
狂野的场景…反映出 男主角性格中桀傲的一面
And the wiIdness of the moors...
...which I think, is mirrored...
...in the wiIdness of HeathcIiff's character.
非常好
ExceIIent! What RacheI has shrewdIy observed here....
瑞秋读得相当透彻
你根本就是照我说的回答
You compIeteIy stoIe my answer!
亲爱的,随便读读就知道了
Honey, that was pretty obvious.
你哪晓得?你根本没过
How wouId you know? You didn't read it!
你有何意见呢?
What do you think? You in the bIue shirt?
穿蓝衬衫这位同学?
我认为这个问题 有很多可能的答案
I think that yours is a question with many possibIe answers.
那就麻烦你举出一个
WouId you care to venture one?
你愿意说一个吗?
你是重复我的话吗?
Are you just repeating me?
好吧,我们看下去
AII right. Let's move on.
好
Okay, then.
你为什么不直接说你没看过?
Why didn't you say you hadn't read the book?
我不希望他认为我很蠢
I didn't want him to think I was stupid.
你看看你多糗
That was reaIIy embarrassing, what happened to you.
菲比 什么?
你那张纸条真是了不起
Your note?
Amazing!
不但没人敢碰我的三明治 而且还开始对我敬畏三分
Not onIy did no one touch my sandwich...
...but peopIe at work are actuaIIy afraid of me.
还有人叫我疯子,疯子盖勒
A guy caIIed me ''MentaI.''
''MentaI GeIIer.''
我一直梦想有这种超酷外号
I've aIways wanted a cooI nickname Iike that.
以前你最酷的外号 就是“尿裤子盖勒”
The best you got in high schooI was ''Wet Pants GeIIer.''
那是饮水机喷到的
It was the water fountain, okay?!
现在有人愿意帮我写报告 我爱什么时候交就什么时候交
Anyway...
...peopIe are writing reports for me...
...pushing back deadIines to fit my scheduIe.
原来对人耍狠就可以呼风唤雨
I teII you, you get tough with peopIe...
...and you can get anything you want.
崔比亚尼,咖啡拿来
Hey, Tribbiani! Give me that coffee! Now!
今天真有意思
This was reaIIy fun.
我本来还怀疑你会不会约我
I've been wondering if you'd ask me out.
你还在怀疑吗?
So you stiII wondering?
我们已经去约会啦
No. We just went out.
你真聪明,我喜欢
You're smart.
I Iike that.
还有蜡烛啊
Oh, candIes!
这是什么?毯子?摄影机? 我的天啊
What is that, a bIanket?
A video camera? Oh, my God!
不是这样…等等啊
I can't beIieve you thought you'd tape us having sex on the first date!
你竟然第一次约会 就想拍下我们上床过程
你好
乔伊,她刚说的…
Joey, is what she just said....
天啊,你还真打算…
Oh, my God!
You're actuaIIy going--
这是怎么回事?
What is going on here?
而且钱德还在家 你是…你是变态吗?
And with ChandIer in the next room. What are you, sick?
我是乔伊啊
I'm Joey.
我本来就恶心
I mean, I'm disgusting.
还拍低成本的A片
I make Iow-budget aduIt fiIms.
你们答应我要更小心的
You promised to be more carefuI!
乔伊的好名声都给你们毁了
The good Joey name's been dragged through the mud!
对不起 抱歉
We're so sorry.
我要把你们的事情说出去
I'm teIIing everyone.
否则内裤跟摄影机的事情 只会让人觉得我是变态猪猡
It's the onIy expIanation that doesn't make me Iook Iike a pig!
等一下,一定有其他方法
No, there's a better expIanation.
你可以说你在拍A片 因为你在…上A片课
TeII them you had to make an aduIt fiIm for your...
...aduIt fiIm cIass.
这理由还不错
I Iike that. But no!
不行,瑞秋在你家 发现我内裤的事又怎么说?
How does that expIain my underwear at your pIace?
不知道
I don't know.
看来你们得出柜承认了
Get ready to come out of the non-gay cIoset.
拜你等等 我保证一定会想出理由
I promise to come up with something. Just give us time.
再多给我们缓几天
好吧,最好让我保住面子
AII right.
But it better make me Iook reaIIy good.
还有…摄影机?
And another thing:
The video camera?
神来之笔!
Nice!
“史前历史博物馆”
罗斯,可以跟你谈谈吗?
当然,唐诺
May I have a word?
Of course, DonaId.
有同事抱怨你最近脾气火爆
We've been getting reports of very angry behavior on your part.
什么?
-What? -Threatening Ietters...
写信威胁大家 拒绝按时交报告
...refusaI to meet deadIines.
还有人说你是疯子
ApparentIy peopIe now caII you MentaI.
是啊
我们希望你找精神科医生谈谈
We want you to speak to a psychiatrist.
不,你不懂,其实是误会
You don't understand. This is so siIIy.
一切要从我的三明治说起
This is aII just because of a sandwich.
三明治?
A sandwich?
我非常会做火鸡三明治
You see, my sister makes these amazing turkey sandwiches.
她的秘诀就是 多夹一片浸过肉汁的面包
Her secret is, she puts an extra sIice of gravy-soaked bread in the middIe.
我称那片为“多汁秘方”
I caII it ''The Moistmaker.''
有一次我把三明治放在冰箱
Anyway, I put my sandwich in the fridge....
你知道吗? 什么?
Oh, you know what?
对不起,应该是我吃掉了
I'm sorry.
I beIieve I ate that.
你吃了我的三明治?
You ate my sandwich?
我一时看错,谁都可能拿错
A simpIe mistake. It can happen to anyone.
是吗?
Oh, reaIIy?
难道你的三明治 也有“多汁秘方”?
Did you confuse it with your own turkey sandwich with a Moistmaker?
没有 难道你没看到上面的纸条?
Do you, perhaps, remember...
...seeing a note on top of it?
我以为那是有人开玩笑 或是随手写的打油诗
There may have been a joke or Iimerick of some kind.
上面清楚地写着那是我的
That said it was...
...my sandwich!
你别激动
Now, caIm down.
可以到我办公室找找 可能垃圾筒里还有剩
Look in my office. Some may be in the trash.
什么?
那个三明治很大
It was quite Iarge. I had to throw most of it away.
我哪里吃得了那么多
你…丢掉我的三明治
You threw my sandwich away?
我的三明治
My sandwich?!
嗨 嗨
What's this book about?
这本书在讲什么?
你这本也没看?
You didn't read it, either?
我本来要看,结果看了别本书
I was going to, but I accidentaIIy read something eIse.
什么?
Vogue.
“时尚杂志”
这个简爱是干嘛的?
So teII me about Jane Eyre.
不行,你应该自己看
No, read it yourseIf.
菲比,别这么假正经嘛
Come on, don't be such a goody-goody.
好吧
Fine.
简爱呢…你会以为她是女人 其实不然,她是生化人
AII right. So, Jane Eyre?
First, you'd think she's a woman, but she's not.
She's a cyborg.
生化人?就是机器人?
A cyborg? Isn't that Iike a robot?
这本书在当时超级先进
This book was Iight years ahead of its time.
抱歉迟到,开始上课吧
Sorry I'm Iate. Let's get started.
大家对简爱有何感想?
What did you think of Jane Eyre?
瑞秋刚跟我讨论过 她有些看法非常有趣
RacheI and I were discussing it, and she had very interesting insights.
请说,瑞秋
Go ahead, RacheI.
谢谢你,菲比
Thank you, Phoebe.
简爱最让我震惊的就是 这本书非常惊世骇俗
What struck me most when reading Jane Eyre...
...was how the book was so ahead of its time.
如果你指的是女性主义 这么说也成
If you're taIking about feminism, I think you're right.
当然有写到女性主义 不过还有机器人
WeII, feminism, yes. But aIso the robots.
嘿 嘿
既然上次要拍摄不成功
Since that video camera thing didn't work out...
我先给你一点预告片段
...I thought that I wouId give you just a IittIe preview.
你没穿衣服
You're naked!
我知道
I know!
罗斯
钱德
摩妮卡
罗斯,你没事吧?
Are you okay?
我很好
I'm fine.
我今天上班去看过精神医生
I saw a psychiatrist at work today.
为什么?
Why?
因为我脾气太暴躁
On account of my rage.
而且最近越来越严重
Which, if I may say, right now is out of controI.
所以他开药丸给我
He gave me a piII for it.
药丸?
A piII?
医生说我对上司大吼大叫 所以应该请假
When the psychiatrist toId me to take a Ieave of absence...
...because I yeIIed at my boss, I started to get worked up again.
我又开始暴跳如雷
所以他要我吃颗镇定剂
So he offered me a tranquiIizer.
我觉得这主意不错
And I thought it was a good idea.
所以就吃了
So I took it.
等等,他们逼你请假?
They're making you take time off work?
而且你也同意?
And you're okay with that?
我不晓得
I don't know.
刚开始不工作可能不习惯
It's going to be weird not having a job for a whiIe.
不过我已经不在乎三明治了
But I definiteIy don't care about my sandwich.
公司逼我看心理医生时 我也很火大
I hate it when they make me see the shrink at my office.
他老说“如果你多爱自己 同事就会更喜欢你”
He's aIways Iike, ''Your coIIeagues wiII Iike you better if you Iike yourseIf better.''
谁需要这套垃圾?
Who needs that?
你啊 我知道
-You do. -I know.
我丢脸丢大了 你竟然还让我说下去
It's so embarrassing! I can't beIieve you Iet me go on Iike that!
对不起
I'm sorry.
你把简爱比做机器战警 实在太爆笑了
It was so funny when you compared Jane Eyre to Robocop.
一点也不好笑
That was not funny!
我太气了
I snapped, okay? You weren't taking the cIass seriousIy.
你根本不想好好上课
菲比,这有什么了不起?
Come on! What is the big deaI?
我以为我们就是一起出去 上课打发时间闹着玩
I thought it'd be something we couId do together.
I thought it wouId be fun.
好玩很重要
Fun is good.
但是我也想学点东西
But I aIso wanted to Iearn.
大家老说在高中学东学西 我却没上过高中
PeopIe taIk about what they Iearned in high schooI. I never went.
所以你真心想上课
So you reaIIy wanted to Iearn.
但是我只想找点乐子
You know, Pheebs, I just wanted to have fun.
你知道你该拉谁去吗?
You know who shouId go?
我知道…
I know! I know! I know!
摩妮卡,问题是你提的
Monica, you asked the question.
天啊,是摩妮卡
Oh, my God, that's Monica!
不是这样…你别误会
离我远点,你这个大变态
You get away from me, you sick, sick, sicko!
怎么啦?
What's going on?
乔伊偷看大家
Joey has got a secret peephoIe!
天啊…
-Oh, no! -Yes, he has a naked picture of Monica!
他有摩妮卡的裸体照片
他拍下我们裸体的样子
He takes naked pictures of us, then he eats chicken and Iooks at them!
还一边吃鸡块一边看
你们看 那是我老耶
Oh! Dude, that's my sister!
给我 等一下,大家先别激动
Give me that!
Wait! Everybody caIm down, okay?
要给我们的老友乔伊 有机会解释他为何如此病态
Let's give our friend a chance to expIain why he's such a big pervert!
我不是变态好吗?
I am not a pervert, okay?
只是…我…其实…
It's just....
I just kind of....
大家听我说,我可以帮他解释
I think I can expIain this.
谢谢
Thank you.
乔伊是性爱狂
Joey's a sex addict.
什么?才怪
What?! No, I'm not!
没关系,不怪你
It's okay! It's good!
这只是一种病
It's a disease.
胡说,我才不是性爱狂
I am not a sex addict!
你明明就是
Yes, you are!
这才能解释最近这一连串的事
That's the onIy way to expIain aII this stuff!
事实不是这样
No, it isn't. It's not.
你也可以说出真相
Because you couId aIso expIain it with the truth!
什么真相?
What is the truth?
怎么回事? 你在说什么?
-What's up? -What's going on?
我跟摩妮卡上床了
I sIept with Monica.
听听大家怎么说?
WeII, Iet's see what everybody thinks of that.
天啊
你跟我老上床?
You sIept with my sister?
对,只在伦敦发生过一次
Yes, but it was--
We just did it once, in London.
这会让我开始抓狂
This is not good for my rage.
摩妮卡,是真的吗?
当然是真的
Is this true?
Of course, it's true.
否则怎么解释这些怪事?
How eIse wouId you expIain aII the weird stuff that's been going on?
是真的
Yes, it's true.
如果只发生过一次
If it happened once, how come we found your underwear in our apartment?
你的内裤 怎么会出现在我们家?
那件内裤是我当天在伦敦穿的 对不对,摩妮卡?
That was the underwear I was wearing that night in London.
Right, Monica?
我想留下来…当纪念品
I guess I wanted to keep it...
...as a souvenir.
天啊,摩妮卡
My God, Monica!
你确定,乔伊? 你确定你不是性爱狂?
Are you sure you're not just a sex addict?
要是有人是性爱狂 那也是摩妮卡
If anyone's a sex addict here, it's Monica.
没错,打从我们自伦敦回来 她就想再勾引我上床
She has been trying to get me back in the sack ever since London!
所以她才拍裸照给你
That's why she gave you a naked picture of herseIf.
这样说得通
That makes sense.
录影机呢?
And the video camera?
摩妮卡?
我架好录影机是为了 引诱乔伊上钩
I guess I set up the video camera to try and entice Joey.
可惜我不吃这套
But, sadIy, I couId not be enticed.
摩妮卡,你不能再这样下去
Monica, this has to stop now.
我知道…不会的
I know, I know.
I know. I wiII, and I wouId appreciate if we aII couId just...
希望大家立刻忘了这件事 以后再也别提起
...drop it immediateIy, and forever.
只要你能抵抗我的魅力
Okay. That is, if you can resist me.
我会尽量努力
-I'II give it my best shot. -Good Iuck.
祝你好运了
不可思议 你还留下乔伊的内裤?
UnbeIievabIe!
You reaIIy kept Joey's underwear?
为什么?你为什么这么做?
Why? Why wouId you do that?
因为我是摩妮卡
I'm Monica.
生性下流
I'm disgusting.
我会跟踪男人 留下他们的内裤
I staIk guys and keep their underpants.
现在终于知道谁是恶心鬼了
I think we've aII Iearned who's disgusting and who's not.
好了,我要开始吃炸鸡了
Now, I'm going to get back to my bucket.
我只吃鸡皮,你们可以吃鸡肉
I'm onIy eating the skin, so the chicken's up for grabs.
你说得很有道理
You were making a good point.
可惜后来被打断
I mean, tiII you got cut off.
那个摩妮卡哪里有病啊?
What's up with that girI Monica?
谁晓得?她不是我朋友
I don't know. I didn't come with her.
好消息,各位 你们猜怎么了?
Hey, everybody! Everybody, guess what!
我说服保罗下周考试
I just convinced CarI to give us a test.
考试?
Test?
开心点,有考试才有进步
Come on! Tests make us aII better Iearners!
对了,应该考申论题
Oh, yeah! We shouId have essay questions!